<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Publications on Jia-Xin Zhuang</title>
    <link>/publications/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Publications on Jia-Xin Zhuang</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 10:21:21 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/publications/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>FUSING METADATA AND DERMOSCOPY IMAGES FOR SKIN DISEASE DIAGNOSIS</title>
      <link>/publications/metanet/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 10:21:21 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publications/metanet/</guid>
      <description>Weipeng Li*, Jiaxin Zhuang*, Ruixuan Wang, Jianguo Zhang, Wei-Shi Zheng.
In Proceedings of the 17th International Symposium on Biomedical Imaging(ISBI), Lowa, USA, 2020.
 Abstract To date, it is still difficult and challenging to automatically classify dermoscopy images. Although the state-of-the-art convolutional networks were applied to solve the classification problem and achieved overall decent prediction results, there is still room for performance improvement, especially for rare disease categories. Considering that human dermatologists often make use of other information (e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CARE: Class Attention to Regions of Lesion for Classification on Imbalanced Data</title>
      <link>/publications/care/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2019 19:48:10 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publications/care/</guid>
      <description>Jiaxin Zhuang*, Jiabin Cai*, Ruixuan Wang, Jianguo Zhang, Weishi Zheng
In Proceedings of the 2nd International Conference on Medical Imaging with Deep Learning(MIDL), London, United Kingdom, 2019
 Abstract To date, it is still an open and challenging problem for intelligent diagnosis systems to effectively learn from imbalanced data, especially with large samples of common diseases and much smaller samples of rare ones. Inspired by the process of human learning, this paper proposes a novel and effective way to embed attention into the machine learning process, particularly for learning characteristics of rare diseases.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>